[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Complete the name of Ron Whites first solo one-hour comedy special: They Call Me _____ _____.", "correct_answer": "Tater Salad", "incorrect_answers": ["Your Excellency", "Mr. White", "Johnnie Walker"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these types of frogs shares its name with an animal that is not a frog?", "correct_answer": "horned frog", "incorrect_answers": ["leopard frog", "tree frog", "arrow frog"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are the names of George Costanzas parents on the TV show Seinfeld?", "correct_answer": "Frank and Estelle", "incorrect_answers": ["Fred and Jean", "Gene and Estelle", "Fred and Harriet"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The nickname Oscar was bestowed on the golden statuette in honor of what person?", "correct_answer": "No one knows for sure", "incorrect_answers": ["Betty Daviss husband", "Oscar Mayer", "Oscar Homolka"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these performers/bands has had the number one and number two albums on the Billboard chart twice?", "correct_answer": "Guns n Roses", "incorrect_answers": ["The Rolling Stones", "Pink Floyd", "Frank Sinatra"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Butterflies do not have lungs. They breathe trough this organ.", "correct_answer": "The abdomen", "incorrect_answers": ["The proboscis", "The eyes", "The legs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 2009 movie is about a couple, their luekemia stricken daughter and the lengths at which they go to save her.", "correct_answer": "My Sisters Keeper", "incorrect_answers": ["The Stepmom", "Marly  Me", "The Notebook"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The oldest known recipe for a beverage still in existence is a recipe for beer.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This invention that forever altered the development of the American West was patented in 1874 by American farmer Joseph Glidden.", "correct_answer": "Barbed wire", "incorrect_answers": ["The scanning disk for future TV sets", "The toothbrush", "Reinforced concrete"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "David E. Weiss was the first mate of the SS Edmund Fitzgerald. The Captain was Ernest M. McSorley.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following movies does this quote come from?\nKarkaroffs Aide: May I have your arm? \nParvati Patil: Arm, leg, Im yours.", "correct_answer": "Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire", "incorrect_answers": ["The Lord of the Rings: The Return of the King", "Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets", "The Lord of the Rings: The Two Towers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which lizard can squirt blood from the corners of its eyes in order to confuse and drive back its enemies?", "correct_answer": "Horned lizard", "incorrect_answers": ["Anole", "Gila monster", "Komodo dragon"]}]